<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>organisation on Computing Club</title>
    <link>https://notes.dmaitre.phyip3.dur.ac.uk/computing-club/tags/organisation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in organisation on Computing Club</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://notes.dmaitre.phyip3.dur.ac.uk/computing-club/tags/organisation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Rebooting for 2021</title>
      <link>https://notes.dmaitre.phyip3.dur.ac.uk/computing-club/updates/reboot/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://notes.dmaitre.phyip3.dur.ac.uk/computing-club/updates/reboot/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to our new members and the regulars!
I&amp;rsquo;ve booked out OC218 (Ogden East Conference Room) for Thursdays at 1300 for the hour. We&amp;rsquo;ll have our first meeting next Thursday, 28 Oct.
OC218 has a capacity of 44 people, so everyone will be able to attend in person if they wish to. For those wishing to join virtually, I&amp;rsquo;ll set up an Owl and you can connect through the Zoom room circulated through the mailing list.</description>
      <content>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to our new members and the regulars!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve booked out OC218 (Ogden East Conference Room) for Thursdays at
1300 for the hour. We&amp;rsquo;ll have our first meeting next Thursday, 28 Oct.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;OC218 has a capacity of 44 people, so everyone will be able to attend
in person if they wish to. For those wishing to join virtually, I&amp;rsquo;ll
set up an Owl and you can connect through the Zoom room circulated through the mailing list.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In our first meeting we can all introduce ourselves and discuss how
we&amp;rsquo;d like to proceed with the club and the content of following
sessions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a lunchtime club, so please do take food if you want to!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Note that there&amp;rsquo;s no expectation of ability or prior knowledge, so everyone please feel very welcome to come
along.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Not that further enticement is required, but tea and coffee will be
provided!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inviting all of Physics to Computing Club</title>
      <link>https://notes.dmaitre.phyip3.dur.ac.uk/computing-club/updates/invite/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://notes.dmaitre.phyip3.dur.ac.uk/computing-club/updates/invite/</guid>
      <description>Historically, the IPPP has held a weekly lunchtime Computing Club. This year we&amp;rsquo;d like to invite everyone in Physics who&amp;rsquo;s interested to join. All career levels are welcome.
We usually run informal seminar style sessions with some open sessions for people to crowd-source solutions to their coding problems. You can see some examples of previous meeting topics at
 https://notes.dmaitre.phyip3.dur.ac.uk/computing-club/topics/ https://shrieking-asylum-67258.herokuapp.com/topics  We also run longer projects for fun when there&amp;rsquo;s interest.</description>
      <content>&lt;p&gt;Historically, the IPPP has held a weekly lunchtime Computing Club. This
year we&amp;rsquo;d like to invite everyone in Physics who&amp;rsquo;s interested to join.
All career levels are welcome.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We usually run informal seminar style sessions with some open sessions
for people to crowd-source solutions to their coding problems. You can
see some examples of previous meeting topics at&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://notes.dmaitre.phyip3.dur.ac.uk/computing-club/topics/&#34;&gt;https://notes.dmaitre.phyip3.dur.ac.uk/computing-club/topics/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://shrieking-asylum-67258.herokuapp.com/topics&#34;&gt;https://shrieking-asylum-67258.herokuapp.com/topics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We also run longer projects for fun when there&amp;rsquo;s interest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To join the mailing list, please send a message to
&lt;a href=&#34;mailto:majordomo@durham.ac.uk&#34;&gt;majordomo@durham.ac.uk&lt;/a&gt; with the following text in the message body:
subscribe ph-complunchclub
You then have to follow the authorisation instructions which will be
emailed back to you. Ensure all emails you send have a plain text body;
authorisation will not work with HTML emails.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If everyone who wants to join fills in their general availability
(ignore the specific dates and treat as weekly availability) on this
poll
&lt;a href=&#34;https://doodle.com/poll/g4rnn55dgxtrt6nd?utm_source=poll&amp;amp;utm_medium=link&#34;&gt;https://doodle.com/poll/g4rnn55dgxtrt6nd?utm_source=poll&amp;amp;utm_medium=link&lt;/a&gt;
I&amp;rsquo;ll pick the best time for everyone and book an appropriately sized
room for us. I&amp;rsquo;ll be in touch with you all via the ph-complunchclub
mailing list once that&amp;rsquo;s sorted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Looking forward to our first meeting!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
